Guide to the Verse Records 1984-2008
University of Chicago Library
Verse. Records
1984-2008
16.75 linear feet (34 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
The Verse Records were processed and preserved as part of the "Uncovering New Chicago Archives Project," funded with support from the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation.
Information on Use
Access
Series II, Administrative and Events, does not include access copies for the compact discs in this series. Researchers will need to consult with staff before requesting material from this series.
Series IV, Restricted, is restricted until 2035.
The collection is open for research.
Historical Note
Verse is an independent literary journal founded in 1984 at Oxford University by Robert Crawford, Henry Hart, and David Kinloch and is currently published by the University of Georgia with assistance from The College of William and Mary and the University of Richmond, VA. Former editors include John Burnside and Lilas Fraser and in 1994, Brian Henry and Andrew Zawacki became the lead editors of Verse.
Verse focuses on international poetry, essays, reviews, and interviews and often presents feature issues on themes or countries. Past features include younger Slovene poets, Australian poetry, Scottish poetry, younger American poets, Mexican poetry, Irish Women poets, Indian poetry, and Russian poetry. The journal has published poems from Ireland, England, Scotland, Russia, Australia, Germany, Spain, Mexico, France, Italy, Cuba, South Africa, Canada, Holland, Sweden, Serbia, Norway, Slovenia, the United States, and other countries. Seamus Heaney said Verse is "One of the most valuable poetry magazines published in the English speaking world."
Robert Crawford was born in Belshill, Lanarkshire, Scotland in 1959 and was educated at Glasgow and Oxford Universities. In 1988, he won the Eric Gregory Award and in 1994 was selected for The New Generation Poet's Promotion. Crawford won the Scottish Arts Council Book Award twice and was recommended for the Poetry Book Society. He is the author of several collections of poetry including A Scottish Assembly (1990), Talkies (1992), Masculinity (1996), Spirit Machines (1999), The Tip of My Tongue (2003), Full Volume (2008). Crawford works as a professor at the University of St. Andrews.
Henry Hart received a B.A. from Darmouth College and a philosophy degree from Oxford University. In 2000 he was the runner up for the Southern Book Critics' Circle Award. Hart's books include: The Ghost Ship (1990), The Rooster Mask (1998), and the Background Radiation (2007). Hart's poetry has appeared in the Gettysburg Review, New Kenyon Review, The Southern Review, The New Yorker Poetry, and Best American Poetry.
David Kinloch was born in Glasglow in 1959 and attended Glasgow and Oxford Universities. He is a recipient of the Robert Louis Stevenson Memorial Award. Kinloch's poetry books include Dustie-Fute (1992), Paris –Forfar (1994), UnTour d'Ecosse (2001), and In My Father's House (2005). After leaving Verse he edited Southfields with Richard Price and also published Informationists pamphlets.
Brian Henry received his B.A. degree from the College of William and Mary and M.F.A. at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst. He won the Alice Fay di Castagnola Award in 2003 and the Cecil B. Hemeley Memorial Award in 2008. Henry is the author of American Incident (2002), Astronaut (2002), Graft (2003), On James Tate (2004), The Verse Book on Interviews (2005), Quarantine (2006), The Shipping Point (2007), and In the Unlikely Event of a Water (2007). Henry's poetry appeared in American Poetry Review, Boston Review, The Canary, Conduit, Denver Quarterly, and The Paris Review. Henry teaches at the University of Richmond.
Andrew Zawacki was born in 1972. In 1995 Andrew Zawacki edited Festschrift for Gustaf Soben with Andrew Joron and The Verse Book of Interviews: 27 Poets on Language, Craft, and Culture with Brian Henry. Zawacki's first book, By Reason of Breakings, won the University of Georgia Contemporary Poetry Series in 2001. Zawacki's second book, Ananbranch, won the Cecil Hemley Memorial Award in 2002. In 2005 Zawacki became a member of Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity and currently teaches at the University of Georgia.
Scope Note
Verse is an independent journal of international poetry, essays, reviews, and interviews. Verse Records are divided into four series: Series I, Correspondence; Series II, Administrative and Events; Series III, Journal Issues; and Series IV, Restricted. The Verse Records contain submissions, correspondence, proofs, manuscripts, newspaper articles, journal issues, reviews, interviews, invoices, press releases, and promotional material. The records document the business and literary aspects of Verse.
Series I, Correspondence, is organized into two subseries. Subseries 1, Alphabetical, contains correspondence arranged alphabetically by last name and includes letters from poets and colleagues, manuscript submissions, and requests for journal copies.
Subseries 2, Editorial, contains correspondence between the various editors, David Kinloch, Robert Crawford, Henry Hart, Brian Henry, and Andrew Zawacki. It is arranged chronologically and includes administrative and personal correspondence. See Series III for additional manuscript submissions.
Series II, Administrative and Events, includes handbills, manuscripts, newspaper articles, author biographies, press releases, submissions, photographs, interviews, reviews, invoices, promotional material, compact discs, grant applications, memorandum agreements, submissions, permission to publish forms, and mailing lists. There are biographies, newspaper articles, and press releases about the editors and poets of Verse. Administrative documents include grant applications, invoices, permission to publish forms, memorandum agreements, and mailing lists. There are photographs, handbills, promotional material, and information on poetry readings and festivals. The compact discs are selections from Verse Press Books, including Letters To Wendy's by Joe Wenderoth and read by James Urbaniak, and F. Train to Coney Island by Joshua Beckman. The Harper magazine includes an article about Joe Wenderoth's Letters to Wendy's, published by Verse Press.
Submissions include works from authors such as Sherman Alexie, Jennifer Atkinson, Mary Jo Bang, Jeanne Marie Beaumont, Andrea Brady, Lee Ann Brown, Sir Thomas Browne, Tina Celona, Jeff Clark, Wyn Cooper, Olena Kalytiak Davis, Ray Di Palma, Timothy Donnelly, Katie Donovan, Thomas Sayers Ellis, Landis Everson, Michael Farrell, Elise Ficarra, Isabelle Garon, James Harms, Lucy Ives, Lisa Jarnot, Jesse Lichtenstein, Timothy Liu, Joanne Lowery, Lisa Lubasch, Gary Lutz, Jennifer MacKenzie, Kathleen McGookey, William Miller, Jonathan Monroe, Jennifer Moxley, Lorine Niedecker, Geoffry Nutter, Jessica Olin, Jena Osman, Ruth Padel, Ethan Paquin, Marjorie Perloff, Heather Ramsdell, Mathew Roth, Tomaz Salamun, Reginald Shepherd, Craig Sherborne, Diann Blakely Shoaf, Penelope Shuttle, Frederick Tibbetts, Chris Tonelli, Karen Volkman, Joshua Weiner, and Susan Wicks.
Series III, Journal Issues, contains correspondence, copyrights agreements, manuscripts, drafts, proofs, notes, interviews, and reviews published in Verse. There are hand-written notations and critiques of drafts and proofs. See Series I for manuscripts kept with correspondence.
Series IV, Restricted, contains a purchase agreement and is restricted until 2035.
Related Resources
Browse finding aids by topic.
Subject Headings
Crawford, Robert, 1959-; Hart, Henry, 1954-; Henry, Brian; Kinloch, David P.; Zawacki, Andrew, 1972-; American poetry--20th century; American poetry -- 21st century; American poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals; American poetry -- 21st century -- Periodicals; American literature -- 20th century -- Periodicals; American literature -- 21st century -- Periodicals; Poetry, Modern -- 20th century; Poetry, Modern -- 20th century -- Periodicals; Small Presses; Verse
INVENTORY
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1: Alphabetical
    - A-Am, 1985-2007, Abbott, Eric Abley, Mark Abramson, Seth Ackerson, Paige Adams, Carrie Adams, Christopher Adams, Joshua Admussen, Nick Agner, Mary Aguilar, Luis Alger, Neil Allan, Kelly Allen, Dick Allen, Esther Allen, K.E. Allen, Richard Allison, John Allison, Will Alsop, Maureen Alvarez, Ivy Amadon, Samuel Amen, John Amichai, Yehuda Ammons, A.R. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - An-Ax, 1987-2007, Anderson, Beth Anderson, Dargie Anderson, James Anderson, Karen Anderson, Maija Anderson, Matt Anderson, Stephanie Andrea, Marianne Angel, Ralph Anglin, Raechel Applewhite, James Aragon, Francisco Archbold, Ismael Archer, Seth Armand, Louis Armantrout, Rae Armitage, Simon Armitank, Simon Armstrong, Glen Arora, Shilpa Ashbery, John Astley, Neil Athey, David Atkins, Cynthia Auchter, Amanda Austin, Mary Axelrod, Steve (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - B-Bal, 1995-2007, Badman, Derik Baer, Bill Bagley, Patrick Bahr, Jeffery Bailey, Erin Baird, Bobby Baker, Andrea Balakian, Peter Balbo, Ned Baldanzi, Linda (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ban-Bena, 1995-2007, Banes, Clay Bang, Mary Jo Barber, Grant Barber, Jenny Barefoot, Walter Barenblat, Rachel Barlow, Randy Bar-Nadav, Hadara Barnwell, Tracy Jo Barnyock, Beth Baron, Jill Barone, Dennis Barrett, Carol Basford, Douglas Bates, Bridgette Battleson, Brenda Baude, Dawn Baus, Eric Beachy, Dan Beard, Dena Beasley, Bruce Beaumont, Jeanne Beaver, Michael Beck, Rachel Becker, Priscilla Becker, Richard Beckman, Joshua Beer, John Beirn, Jane Bell, Josh Belz, Aaron Benak, Vesna (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Benn-Blac, 1996-2007, Bennett, Carrie Bennett, Guy Berger, Don Berger, Zackary Berman, D.C. Bernes, Jasper Bernstein, Charles Berridge, David Berrigan, Anselm Berry, Graham Berry, Simeon Berry, Wendell Besser, Kate Best, B.J. Bettridge, Joel Bezanson, Graeme Biarujia, Javant Bibbins, Mark Bickerstaffe, Daniel Bien, Peter Bierds, Linda Biggins, Michael Bilbrey, Mark Birns, Nicholas Bishop, Charlotte Bishop, Judith Black, Ezekiel (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Blai-Bour, 1995-2008, Blair, Chad Blair, David Blair, Jenn Blakely, Diann Blakesley, David Blatnik, Andrej Bleecker, Alex Block, Summer Blumenthal, Michael Bode-Lang, Andrew Bohanan, Audrey Bohince, Paul Boland, Eavan Bolden, Emma Bolin, Ally Boller, Diane Bonanno, Michael Bond, Bruce Boren, Molly Boruch, Marianne Bossom, Linda Bouchard, Daniel Boulay, Charlotte Boully, Jenny Bourgeois, Anna Bourne, Daniel (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bouv-Broe, 1987-2006, Bouvier, Geoff Bowdan, Janet Bowden, Alison Bowden, Rus Boyle, Peter Boynton, Victoria Brady, Andrea Brady, Veronica Brahic, Beverley Braticevic, Tina Britton, Iain Brodak, Molly Brodeur, Mark Broemer, Marlene (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Broo-Burk, 1985-2007, Brooker, Gregory Brookhiser, Richard Brooks, Bob Brooks, Dianne Broom, Sarah Brown, Andrew Brown, Ashley Brown, Nickole Brown, Pam Brown, Ronald Brown, Steven Brown, Tony Browne, Laynie Buchanan, Oni Buchsbaum, Julianne Buffam, Suzanne Bumstead, Leslie Burch, Jennifer Burchfield, Dana Burger, Eric Burkard, Michael (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Burn-By, 1993-2005, Burns, Joanne Burns, Sloan Burnside, John Burris, Sidney Burt, Stephen Busch, Trent Butt, Anabeth Byrd, Brigitte Byrne, Mairead Bywater, Arielle (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - C-Chan, 1995-2007, Caddy, David Cafferty, Catherine Campana, Joseph Campbell, Allison Campbell, James Campo, Rafael Cantwell, Kevin Cape, Jonathan Capildeo, Vahni Caples, Garrett Capozzi, James Cardenal, Ernesto Cardinale, Jenna Carlson, Donna Carlson, Nancy Carlson, Sten Carnevale, Alex Carr, Julie Carrier, C.S. Carrington, Patrick Carroll, Rachel Carruth, Hayden Carson, Ciaran Carter, John Carver, Evan Casamassima, Christophe Casper, Robert Cassian, Nina Catania, Amy Catanzano, Amy Caze, Antoine Cecil, Richard Cecil, Susan Celona, Tina Chamberlin, Kathy Chambers, Christopher Chang, Jason Chang, Jeff Chang, Jennifer Chang, Victoria (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Chap-Cof, 1986-2007, Chapis, Jennifer Chapman, J’Lyn Chapman, Lee Chapman, Patrick Charles, Bryan Chase, Karen Checkoway, Julie Chelotti, Dan Chernoff, Maxine Chestnut, Tina Chestnut, Vic Choffel, Julie Chokoisky, Simon Christian, Jack Christie, A.V. Christle, Heather Ciccotelli, Darin Cincala, Todd Ciotola, Andrew Clanchy, Kate Clare, Carolina Clark, Charlie Clark, Jackie Clark, Jeff Clark, John Clark, Joshua Clark, Lauren Clark, Tom Clausen, Christopher Clay, Adam Cleveland, Stephanie Clifford, Catherine Cobler, Anya Codish, Eitan Cofer, Judith (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Coh-Cool, 1986-2007, Cohen, Lyndsey Cohen, Marc Colangelo, Carmon Colburn, Nadia Cole, Andrew Cole, Lucinda Coleman, R.D. Collins, Jennifer Collins, Martha Comerford, Sarah Compton, Diane Compton, Shanna Conforto, Carla Conners, Peter Conoley, Gillian Consenstein, Peter Contogenis, Constantine Contreras, Renee Cooley, Nicole Cooley, Peter Coolidge, Clark (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Coop-Cou, 2000-2007, Cooperman, Matthew Copeland, Joelean Cordner, Sheila Corey, Joshua Corey, Stephen Corless-Smith, Martin Corrie, Dan Corwin, Nina Cory, Cynie Cosgriff, Robert Costello, Bonnie Couch, Clayton Coudriet, Daniel Court, Karen Folder 7: Cov-Cu, 1995-2007 Covey, Bruce Covino, Peter Coyle, Craig Coyle, William Craft, Kevin Craig, J.P. Craig, Michael Craige, Betty Creeley, Robert Crittenden, Chris Cronin, Margie Croome, Rodney Cruickshank-Hagenbuckle, Geoffrey Cruz, Cynthia Culliton, Patrick Culver, Lyndsey Cumming, Robert Currin, Jen Curry, Crystal Cushman, Stephen Cutter, Weston (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - D-Dav, 1999-2007, Dahl, Patricia Dahlen, Beverly Daly, Catherine Dare, Robin Darnell, Marcus David, Ashley Davidson, Chad Davies, Adam Davis, Alexis Davis, Christina Davis, Christopher Davis, Ed Davis, Garrett Davis, Garrick Davis, Jordan Davis, Lisa Davis, Peter (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Daw-Der, 1995-2006, Dawes, Nic Day, Cort Day, Sarah Debeljak, Aleš DeBoer, Bernhard DeCarteret, Mark DeCesare, Henry Dee, Liza Deininger, Craig de la Flor, Neil de la Torre, Monica Denham, Robert deNiord, Chard DeNiro, Alan Dennigan, Darcie Denning, Susan Dentz, Shira Derkac, Lana Derrick, Paul (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Det-Dol, 1988-2008, Detorie, Michelle Devine, Lisa Di, Xue Dick, Jennifer Dickey, Christopher Dickey, James Dickinson, Amy Dickson, Barry Didato, Thom Dietz, Michael Dille, Carolyn DiMaggio, Kenneth Dimkovoska, Lidija DiPalma, Ray Ditchfield, Sheila Djordjevic, Milan Dobyns, Stephen Dockins, Mike Doherty, Garrett Doller, Sandra (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Dom-Dor, 1998-2008, Domitrovich, Jim Donahue, Bernard Donahue, Joseph Donnelly, Timothy Donovan, Katie Dordick, Barry Dore, Deirdre Doris, Stacey Dorjee, Tsultrim Dorsett, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Dot-Dy, 1998-2008, Doty, Mark Dougherty, Sean Dow, Mark Downing, Brandon Doyle, Ben Doyle, James Drexel, John Dubie, Norman Duende, Elena Duff, Valerie Duffin, K.E. Dumanis, Michael Dunn, Douglas Durand, Marcella Durgin, Patrick Dworkin, Craig Dydo, Ulla (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - E-Er, 1984-2006, Eagleton, Terry Eberhart, Richard Ebersole, John Ebinger, Steve Edgar, Chris Edgar, Stephen Edwards, Joshua Egejuru, Phanuel Eichin, Florence Elarkin, Ed Ellis, Phillip Ellis, Thomas Emery, Christopher Engel, Jeanne Ennis, John Enright, Mary Epstein, Daniel Erdrich, Louise Eric, Kate (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Es-Ey, 1993-2007, Eshleman, Caryl Eshleman, Clayton Espada, Martin Estes, Angie Etter, Carrie Evans, Nicola Evans, Steve Ewing, Robyn Eyth, Melanie (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - F-Finch, 1995-2007, Factor, Jenny Fagan, Kate Fagenblat, Michael Fagin, Larry Fallon, Peter Fambrough, Monica Farrell, Michael Fathi, Farnoosh Fattaruso, Paul Fay, Sarah Feinman, Alvin Feirstein, Fredwick Felder, Brian Fernandez, Robert Fieled, Adam Finch, Annie Finch, Peter (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Finck-Four, 2000-2007, Fincke, Gary Findura, John Fink, Thomas Finkelstein, Caroline Finnell, Dennis Firestone, Jennifer Fishman, Lisa Flaherty, Ryan Fletcher, Joe Flinn, Mary Fliss, Brad Florio, Michael Flowers, Charles Fong, Herman Forche, Carolyn Fosco, Cory Fourcade, Dominique (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Fous-Ful, 1996-2006, Foust, Graham Foust, Rebecca Fox, Sarah Francis, David Franklin, Jennifer Fraser, Lilas Freeman, Barbara Freeman, Molly Frere-Jones, Sasha Friebert, Stuart Fried, Phillip Friedlander, Ben Frisardi, Andrew Fuhrman, Joanna Fulton, Alice Fulton, Lee Fulton, Robin (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - G-Gin, 1987-2008, Gabbert, Elisa Gailey, Jeannine Galef, David Gallagher, Chris Gallagher, Katherine Gallaher, John Galvin, Brendan Galvin, James Gammarino, Thomas Ganassi, Ian Gander, Forrest Gannon, Mary Gardner, David Garin, Marita Garner, Ebun Garza, Elisa Gascoyne, David Gatza, Geoffrey Gay, Erin Geddie, Robin Gekoski, Rick Gelsinger, Eric Gendron, James Genoways, Ted Gerkis, Caroline Gerlach, Lee Gery, John Gewanter, David Ghigna, Charles Gibson, Dobby Giddens, Elizabeth Giesler, Jimmy Giffin, Joseph Giffin, Lawrence Gifford, Barry Gigante, Denise Gilbey, David Gilley, Emily Giménez-Roselló, Carmen Gingras, Jesse (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Gioia, Dana, 1986-2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Gioia, Dana, 1986-2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Giz-Gra, 1986-2008, Gizzi, Peter Glenum, Lara Glover, Beth Glück, Louise Godfrey, Landon Godston, Daniel Gold, Meg Goldberg, Lawrence Goldstein, David Goldstein, Sarah Goldsworthy, Peter Gonsalves, Joy Gonzalez, Ray Göransson, Johannes Gordimer, Nadine Gordon, Fran Gordon, Noah Gorvine, Tara Gouirand, Rae Goumas, Yannis Grace, Alexandra Grace, Andrew Grafton, Grace Graham, Loren Grant, Adriana Graves, Michael Gray, Kathryn Gray, Martin (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Gre-Gro, 1986-2008, Green, Chris Greenberg, Alvin Greenberg, Arielle Greenhouse, Stuart Greenlaw, Lavinia Greiner, Corinne Grenier, Arpine Grennan, Eamon Gridley, Sarah Grinnell, Tracey Grinwis, James Gritsman, Andrey Groarke, Vona Gross, Philip Grossman, Allen (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Gru-Gu, 2001-2007, Gruber, David G’Schwind, Stephanie Guest, Paul Guinness, Selina Guinzio, Carolyn Gunn, Thom Gunton, Dave Gur, Efrat Gutstein, Daniel (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - H-Hame, 1984-2008, Hacker, Marilyn Hadas, Rachel Hagstrom, Jack Hahn, Robert Haight, Ian Hales, Daniel Hall, Donald Hall, Judith Hall, Kate Halman, Talat Halpern, Daniel Halsey, Christine Ham, Bob Hamby, Barbara Hamer, Terri (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Hami-Hart, 1996-2006, Hamilton, David Hamilton, Jeff Hamilton-Emery, Chris Han, Susie Hanlon, Kristen Hannah, Sophie Hannan, Maryanne Hansen, Michael Hansen, Tom Hanson, Danielle Hanson, Josh Hanssen, Beatrice Hanus, Richard Harmon, Joshua Harms, James Harp, Gerald Harp, Jerry Harris, Erina Harrison, Jeffrey Harrod, Lois Harry, Jann S. Harryman, Carla Hart, Kevin Hartman, M.L. Hartman, Tom (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Harv-Hel, 1984-2008, Harvey, Matthea Harvey, Sean Hasan, Raza Hatch, Janet Hauke, Nathan Hawk, Rachael Hawke, John Hawkes-Howat, Valerie Hawkins, J. Todd Hawley, Anthony Hawn, Adam Headlam, Kristin Healey, Stephen Healey, Steve Healy, Randolph Heaney, Seamus Hecht, Anthony Heck, Evelyn Heffernan, Michael Heide, Anne Heise, William Thomas Hejinian, Lyn Heller, Michael Hellyin, Kevin Helms, Laura (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Hem-Hie, 1998-2006, Hemensley, Kris Hena, Omaar Henderson, Audrey Henderson, Brian Henderson, Derek Hendrick, Michael Henehan, Kira Hennefrand, Elizabeth Hennessy, Christopher Henning, Sara Henriksen, Matt Herbert, W.N. Hero, Claire Herron, Patrick Hershon, Robert Heston, Brian Heyen, William Hicok, Bob Hierl, Sebastian (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hig-Hok, 1997-2007, Higgins, Tiffany Hilbert, Ernest Hill, Casey Hill, Craig Hill, Geoffrey Hillman, Brenda Hilton, Nelson Hodge, Roger Hoff, Anne-Christine Hoff, James Hoggard, James Hoks, Nathan (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Hol-Howe, 1984-2008, Holden, Jonathan Holladay, Hilary Hollahan, Eugene Hollander, Katherine Holler, David Holley, Margaret Hollowell, Erin Holmes, Janet Hong, Cathy Hoover, Paul Hopler, Jay Hornik, Jessica Hosea, Chris Houlihan, John Houng, Cynthia Howe, Kristen Howe, Susan (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hows-Hy, 1988-2006, Howsare, Erika Hsiao, Irene Huffman, Khalil Hughes, Ted Hugo, Anne Hume, Christine Hummel, Thomas Hummell, Austin Hummer, Terry Hummer, Theo Hund, Christopher Hundley, Nick Huset, Zeb Huskey, Lori Hutcheson, Jo Huteson, Greg Hutton, Lizzie Hymans, Don (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - I, 2003-2007, Iddings, Cecily Iglenum, Lara Illich, Donald Inside, Aphoenix Irwin, Mark Isles, John Israeli, Henry Ives, Lucy Izenberg, Oren (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - J-Je, 1988-2007, Jackson, James Jackson, Richard Jackson, Rick Jackson, Stacy Nathaniel Jacques, Jean Jaime, Michael Jamie, Kathleen Jane, Barbara Janke, Chris Jarnot, Lisa Jasper, Matt Jauss, David Jelnikar, Ana Jenike, Lesley Jenkins, Alan Jenkins, Louis Jenks, Allison (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, 1997-2007, Johnson, Daniel Johnson, J. Johnson, Miranda Johnson, Paul Johnson, Peter (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Johnst-Ju, 1989-2007, Johnston, Andrew Johnston, Fred Johnston, Devin Johnstone, Rosemarie Jones, Jackie Jones, Kelina Jones, Nathan Jones, Suzanne Jordan, Barbara Jorgensen, Edmund Joritz, Jane Joron, Andrew Joseph, Lawrence Justice, Donald (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - K-Kei, 1988-2007, Kalamaras, George Kallet, Jeff Kane, Paul Kaplan, Debbie Karhi, Jeanette Karpilovsky, Suzanne Kartsonis, Sophia Kaschock, Kirsten Katko, Justin Katz, Joy Katz, Vincent Kaufman, Ellen Kaufman, Erica Kaufman, Stuart Kaupang, Aby Keckler, W.B. Keenaco, Gus Keenan, Michael Keene, Jarret Keeney, Scott Keesbury, Aron Keiley, Lizbeth (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Kel-Ken, 1995-2005, Kelen, Steve Kellas, Anne Kelleher, Carl Kelsey, Karla Kendall, Tim Kennedy, David Kennedy, Jake Kenney, Richard Kenny, Sir Anthony Kenwood, Nina Kenyon, Jane (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Kh-Kinl, 1985-2007, Khallip, Jacques Kiely, Sean Kiesselbach, Dore Kilfara, Kenny Killebrew, Paul Killough, Ann Kim, Brian Kim, Flora Kimball, Jack King, Amy King, Cindy Kinloch, David (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Kinsella, John, 1995-2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Kir-Koc, 1991-2008, Kirby, Barney Kirby, David Kirk, Donna Kirksey, Lisa Kirsch, Adam Kirtley, Cristen Kissane, Andy Kitche, Heidi Klane, Matthew Klatt, Lewis Klein, Laurie Kleinzahler, August Klink, Joanna Kluge, Christine Knoeller, Christian Knox, Caroline Knox, Jennifer Kobylarz, Philip Koch, James Koch, Kenneth Kociemba, Alice (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Koe-Ku, 1993-2007, Koehn, David Koeneke, Rodney Koestenbaum, Wayne Koethe, John Koffman, Roald Komunyakaa, Yusef Koneazny, Paula Konopka, Autumn Konyalian, Arpine Koo, Jason Koon, Mary Kosmicki, Greg Kostelanetz, Rich Krajeski, Jenna Krasovec, Metka Kravetz, Lee Krisak, Len Krump, David Kryah, Joshua Kubasak, Sharon Kuhl, Nancy Kusar, Marjetka Kushner, Dale (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - L-Lat, 1993-2007, Labbe, Jason Lacavaro, Tony Lamoureux, Mark Landau, Deborah Landers, Susan Lang, Abigail Lang, Sarah Langan, Steve Larimer, Kevin Larsen, Laura Larsen, Wolf Lasher, Susan Lasky, Dorothea Latimer, Nicholas Latrenta, Amanda Latta, John (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Lau-Lee, 1989-2007, Lau, David Lauer, Brett Laurey, Stephanie Lawler, Christa Lawler, Patrick Lawrence, Anthony Lawrence, David Lazer, Hank Le, Nam Lea, Sydney Lease, Joseph Lederer, Katherine Lee, David Lee, Gareth Lee, Juliette Lee, Li-Young (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Leh-Lev, 1988-2006, Lehman, David Leichum, Laura Leja, Kristine Lemon, Alex Lenier, Sue Leon, Jon Leonard, John Lerner, Ben Lessley, Shara Levin, Phillis (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Lew-Li, 1992-2007, Lew, Emma Lewis, Lesle Li, Bing Lichtenstein, Jesse Liddy, James Liefer, Allison Lietz, Chad Lilly, Rebecca Limon, Ada Lindgren, Petter Lineberger, James Lingafelter, Amy Link, Jon Liu, Timothy Livingood, Jeb (Box 7, Folder 7)